export const WORDS = [
    { question: "What is the largest land mammal?", answer: "elephant" },
    {
        question: "Which animal has an extremely long neck and lives in Africa?",
        answer: "giraffe",
    },
    {
        question: "What bird cannot fly and lives in cold regions?",
        answer: "penguin",
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which animal hops on its hind legs and carries its young in a pouch?",
        answer: "kangaroo",
    },
    {
        question:
            "What aquatic mammal is known for being intelligent and friendly?",
        answer: "dolphin",
    },
    {
        question: "What color is a vibrant mix of blue and green?",
        answer: "turquoise",
    },
    {
        question: "What Italian dish has layers of pasta, sauce, and cheese?",
        answer: "lasagna",
    },
    {
        question: "What type of French pastry has a crescent shape?",
        answer: "croissant",
    },
    {
        question: "What typical American breakfast is round and served with syrup?",
        answer: "pancake",
    },
    {
        question: "What Mexican food is rolled and can contain various fillings?",
        answer: "burrito",
    },
    {
        question: "What South American country has Buenos Aires as its capital?",
        answer: "Argentina",
    },
    {
        question:
            "What country is a city-state known for its cleanliness and order?",
        answer: "Singapore",
    },
    {
        question: "What country is home to kangaroos and koalas?",
        answer: "Australia",
    },
    {
        question: "In which European country is the city of Lisbon located?",
        answer: "Portugal",
    },
    {
        question:
            "What country is famous for its pastries and Hans Christian Andersen's tales?",
        answer: "Denmark",
    },
    {
        question:
            "What weather phenomenon involves a rotating column of high-speed wind?",
        answer: "tornado",
    },
    {
        question: "What storm involves heavy snow and strong winds?",
        answer: "blizzard",
    },
    {
        question: "What profession designs buildings and urban spaces?",
        answer: "architect",
    },
    {
        question:
            "What profession is dedicated to researching and discovering new knowledge?",
        answer: "scientist",
    },
    {
        question: "What profession performs or creates music as a career?",
        answer: "musician",
    },
];
